<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Book on Gangleri</title>
    <link>https://gangleri.io/tags/book/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Book on Gangleri</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <copyright>Powered by [Hugo](http://gohugo.io).</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 May 2011 19:54:30 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://gangleri.io/tags/book/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>HTML5 Up and Running</title>
      <link>https://gangleri.io/post/html5_up_and_running/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2011 19:54:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gangleri.io/post/html5_up_and_running/</guid>
      <description>Given the hype you might be forgiven for mistaking HTML5 as the 2nd coming. But all joking aside this is a significant step for the web but what does it really offer web developers? Well this is a question that I feel is answered in HTML5 Up and Running.
First thing to point out is that this book at just under 200 pages, is not an in-depth coverage of all the new features coming with HTML5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EBook Management</title>
      <link>https://gangleri.io/post/calibre/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2011 19:54:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gangleri.io/post/calibre/</guid>
      <description>Since getting my Kindle, I&amp;rsquo;ve amassed more and more eBooks and one of the best tools I&amp;rsquo;ve found to manage all these books in Calibre. This is a free and open-source tool that helps you manage your library of eBooks and best of all it&amp;rsquo;s available for Windows, Mac, and Linux users.
Calibre is rather like iTunes for your eBook; it allows you to define metadata for your books such as tags that allow you later to search for books.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Java The Code Parts</title>
      <link>https://gangleri.io/post/java_the_good_parts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2011 19:54:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gangleri.io/post/java_the_good_parts/</guid>
      <description>I’m a fan of the effective series of books (Effective Java, Effective C#, etc.) and was, therefore, looking forward to this book hoping to pick up a few gems I’d yet to discover. To be blunt, I was disappointed. The book is well written and concise, however having done significant Java development I found this book more of a nostalgic reminder of the advances Java had given us when it first appeared in the late nineteen nineties.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>97 Things Every Programmer Should Know</title>
      <link>https://gangleri.io/post/97_things_every_programmer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2011 19:54:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gangleri.io/post/97_things_every_programmer/</guid>
      <description>Following on from 97 Things Every Software Architect Should Know and the less heard of 97 Things Every Project Manager Should Know this book full of 97 things programmers should know. This book contains insight from many of today&amp;rsquo;s best developers cutting code day after day.
Like the other books in this series, this book is extremely well written and presented in a very digestible format as each of the 97 points has a maximum of two pages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Passionate Programmer</title>
      <link>https://gangleri.io/post/passionateprogrammer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2010 19:54:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gangleri.io/post/passionateprogrammer/</guid>
      <description>Software development to me is a career that offers an excellent opportunity to be passionate about what you do. On the flip side, it&amp;rsquo;s also easy to slip into a mundane routine buried beneath layers of bureaucracy. In which your passion fades and instead of the outstanding career you dreamed of you become an average programmer drifting from day to day ticking boxes going through the motions in the belief that titles and promotion are the keys to a safe job and happiness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ReWork: Change the Way You Work Forever</title>
      <link>https://gangleri.io/post/rework/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2010 19:54:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gangleri.io/post/rework/</guid>
      <description>Buy this book!! I can&amp;rsquo;t emphasise that enough; this book is clear advice on how to go about starting up a project and growing it from your pet project to a product that you can be passionate about and make work for you as a business.
Rework is not a very wordy book, and as a result, it&amp;rsquo;s a book you can read very quickly, with each point the authors wish to raise is presented in only a few pages of large, clean fonts that are easy on the easy on your eyes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Not How Good You Are, It&#39;s How Good You Want To Be</title>
      <link>https://gangleri.io/post/itsnothowgood/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2010 19:54:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gangleri.io/post/itsnothowgood/</guid>
      <description>On a recent trip to London for DevWeek, I had a bit of time to wander around the Barbican&amp;rsquo;s art gallery. In there, there are loads of interesting designs for things from seats to buildings. However one of the most interesting things I found was in the gift shop. It&amp;rsquo;s a small book with an unpretentious cover. However, the very title just jumped out at me &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s Not How Good You Are, It&amp;rsquo;s How Good You Want To Be.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>